Shahrzad Shashaani

 ▼ Tehran, Iran
 Lehran, Iran
 +989122190127
 Image: shahrzad-shashaani@gmail.com
 In linkedin.com/in/shahrzad-shashaani

https://shahrzad-sh.github.io/Shahrzad-Shashaani.github.io/ https://github.com/Shahrzad-sh

₽ Profile

An enthusiastic and motivated computer scientist who contributes to Artificial Intelligence, Machine Learning, and Deep Learning projects. Experienced and proficient in various programming languages and frameworks relevant to Machine Learning and Deep Learning.

My research interests include Machine Learning, Deep Learning, and Computer Vision in Robotics and Health with supervised and self-supervised learning methods.

Education

09/2020 - 02/2023 Master of Science in Artifitial Inteligence

Tehran, Iran K. N. Toosi University of Technology ∂

World University Rankings 2021: 800-1000th, 2022: 1000-1200th ∂

GPA: 4/4 (18.95/20)

Ranking: 1st (Among ~25 Students)

Thesis Title: Using Convolutional Neural Networks for Off-road Path Detection in Self-driving

Cars

Supervisor: Prof. Mohammad Teshnehlab ∂

09/2016 - 09/2020 Bachelor of Science in Computer Engineering

Tehran, Iran K. N. Toosi University of Technology ∂

World University Rankings 2021: 800-1000th, 2022: 1000-1200th ${\mathscr D}$ GPA: 3.89/4 (18.53/20) / Last two years' GPA: 4/4 (19.08/20)

Ranking: 3rd (Among ~47 Students)

Thesis Title: Hospital Data Analysis Using Nonlinear Regression and Fuzzy Neural Networks

Supervisor: Prof. Mohammad Teshnehlab *⊘*

☐ Publications

Network Intrusion Detection with Limited Labeled Data ℰ

Lotfi S, Modirrousta M, **Shashaani S**, Amini S, Aliyari Shoorehdeli M. **Network Intrusion Detection with Limited Labeled Data**. *arXiv preprint arXiv:2209.03147*. 2022.

Covid-19 Detection based on Blood Test Parameters using Various Artificial Intelligence Methods ⊗

Khanjani K, **Shashaani S**, Mehralian S, Jalaeian-Zaferani E, Teshnehlab M, Khodadadian A, Heitzinger C, Nadji A, *et al.*. **Covid-19 Detection based on Blood Test Parameters using Various Artificial Intelligence Methods**. *Advances in Precision Nutrition, Personalization, and Healthy Aging (Springer)*. 2022;19:506-532.

Rapid COVID-19 Screening Based on the Blood Test using Artificial Intelligence Methods ⊗

Mehralian S, Jalaeian Zaferani E, **Shashaani S**, Kashefinishabouri F, Teshnehlab M, Sokhandan HA, Dibaji Forooshani ZS, Montazer B, Joneidi Z, Vafapeyvand M. **Rapid COVID-19 Screening Based on the Blood Test using Artificial Intelligence Methods**. *Journal of Control*. 2021 Feb 10;14(5):131-140.

02/2023 – present **Teaching Assistant**

Deep Learning

Artificial Intelligence Department, K. N. Toosi University of Technology ∂

Instructor: Prof. Mohammad Teshnehlab 🔗

09/2022 - 02/2023

Teaching Assistant

Tehran, Iran

Neural Networks

Artificial Intelligence Department, K. N. Toosi University of Technology ∂

Instructor: Prof. Mohammad Teshnehlab *⊗*

02/2022 - 06/2022

Teaching Assistant

Tehran, Iran

Deep Learning

Artificial Intelligence Department, K. N. Toosi University of Technology ∂

Instructor: Prof. Mohammad Teshnehlab ∂

09/2021 - 02/2022

Teaching Assistant

Tehran, Iran

Neural Networks

Artificial Intelligence Department, K. N. Toosi University of Technology &

Instructor: Prof. Mohammad Teshnehlab ∂

09/2019 - 02/2020

Teaching Assistant

Tehran, Iran Algorithm Design

Computer Engineering Department, K. N. Toosi University of Technology ℰ

Instructor: Dr. Amin Nikanjam ∂

Professional Experience

01/2019 - 02/2023

Research Assistant

Tehran, Iran

K. N. Toosi ISLAB(Intelligent Systems Laboratory)

Main Experience

• Worked as a member of the COVID-19 diagnosis project

• Worked as a member of the path detection project

Reference: Prof. Mohammad Teshnehlab *⊘*

07/2021 - 07/2022

Part-time developer

Tehran, Iran

Araye Pardaz Limited Company (Software Engineering Startup)

Main Experience

Learning how to work in an Agile environment during the software development phase

• Developing a basic database

• Developing Admin panel

12/2021 - 06/2022

Part-time Developer

Tehran, Iran

TelC International Communication Company *∂*

Main Experience

• Developing some parts of an existing database using MySQL

• Finding and extracting useful information from registered records

• Developing a simple recommender system for defined customer care app using Python

09/2020 - 12/2021

Tehran, Iran

Team Member of SR2119 Social Robot Developing Project

AICell Startup ∂

Main Experience

• Machine Vision

• Face Detection and Recognition

Face Tracking

• Age-Gender Estimation

Catalog Link: SR2119 Robot ∂

Reference: Mr. Sajjad Amini [s_amini@sharif.edu]

06/2019 – 09/2019 *Internship*

Tehran, Iran Assessment of Electronic Health Record System of Iran Health Organization, Iran

Telecommunication Research Center(ITRC) ∂

Main Experience

• Testing Electronic Health Record System (SEPAS)

• Developing Record Comparator Tool with Python

Reference: Mr. Mohammad Azadnia [azadnia@itrc.ac.it]

Tehran, Iran Android Application, Arena Group

Main Experience

• Developing Android Program for Students Curriculum Management

Download Link: Sakoo App ∂



Master

- Machine Learning (4/4)
- Deep Learning (4/4)
- Machine Vision (4/4)
- Evolutionary Computing (4/4)
- Multi-agent Systems (4/4)
- Pattern Recognition (3/4)

Bachelor

- Foundations of Computer Vision (4/4)
- Graph Theory and Algorithms (4/4)
- Embedded and Real-Time Systems (4/4)
- Data Structure (4/4)
- Database (4/4)
- Algorithm Design (3/4)
- Artificial Intelligence and Expert Systems (3/4)

Honors, Awards and Grants

2020 – 2022	Ranked 1st (out of ~25 Students) MSc Degree, Artificial Intelligence Department, K. N. Toosi University of Technology
2020 – 2022	Received Full Tuition Fee Waiver Scholarship K. N. Toosi University of Technology
2020	Credited for M.Sc. Degree K. N. Toosi University of Technology
2020	Won the 3rd Place in the Problem Solving Competitions of Shahid Babaei Project Smartization Field, Iran National Elite Foundation (Rah Neshan)
2018 – 2020	Included in Dean's List for 3 Semesters K. N. Toosi University of Technology
2017 – 2020	Received Excellent Students Scholarship, Kanoon Farhangi Amoozesh K. N. Toosi University of Technology
2016 – 2020	Ranked 3rd (Out of ~53 Students) BSc Degree, Computer Engineering Department, K. N. Toosi University of Technology

2016 - 2020 **Received Full Tuition Fee Waiver Scholarship**

K. N. Toosi University of Technology

2016 Ranked within the top 1% of Iranian University Entrance Exam for Bachelor's Degree

2012 Won the 2nd place in the Karate(Kata) championship in provincial competitions

Projects

2020 - 2022 Using Convolutional Neural Networks for Off-road Path Detection in Self-driving Cars

The Master's Thesis

- Using off-road dataset (Freiburg Forest Dataset)
- Developing a layer-wise train for CNNs
- Using BEL (Brain Emotional Learning) architecture

2021 **Edeg detection using PiDiNet**

Final project of Machine Vision

- Inspired by an article named pixel difference networks for efficient edge detection *∂*
- PiDiNet was a Deep CNN which uses both traditional edge detection operators and Convolutional operations at the same time.

2020 Hospital Data Analysis Using Nonlinear Regression and Fuzzy Neural Networks

The Bachelor's Thesis

- Using blood test results for COVID-19 detection
- Speeding up the process and reducing the price of COVID-19 detection

2020 Persian-Handwriting-Recognition tool for a specific type of form

Final project of Computer Vision course

- Collecting a small dataset of Persian handwritten letters and digits
- Detecting information parts of the form using OpenCV contours
- Training two separate CNNs to classify handwritten Persian letters and digits
- Giving extracted contours to trained CNNs and showing predicted results



Deep Learning Libraries and Frameworks

Pytorch/TensorFlow/Keras

Programming Languages and Tools

Python / MATLAB / Weka / C / C++ / Java

Computer Engineering

Git / Linux / Agile Development

Machine Learning Libraries and Frameworks

scikit-learn / OpenCV / Dlib / mediapipe

Other Libraries and Frameworks

Numpy / Pandas / Matplotlib

Database

MySQL / Microsoft SQL Server

Canguages

Persian **Arabic Engilsh** Native

IELTS: 7.5 (Speaking:7 | Listening:7.5 |

Reading:8.5 | Writing:6.5)

Elementary proficiency

⅔ References

Dr. Mohammad Teshnehlab, *Professor*, K. N. Toosi University of Technology, Tehran, Iran teshnehlab@eetd.kntu.ac.ir, (+98)-021-84062323

Dr. Babak Nasersharif, *Assistant Professor*, K. N. Toosi University of Technology bnasersharif@kntu.ac.ir, (+98)-021-84062268

Dr. Saeed Farzi, *Assistant Professor*, K. N. Toosi University of Technology saeedfarzi@kntu.ac.ir, (+98)-21-84062-414

Dr. Ali Ahmadi, *Associate Professor*, K. N. Toosi University of Technology ahmadi@kntu.ac.ir

♂ Interests

Working out, Drawing, Watching movies and TV series, Listening to music or podcast